The fin's been smashed!
!دُمّرت الزعنفة
The nerve of that damn runt!
كيف يجرؤ ذلك الشقي؟
Is he trying to destroy the ship?!
!أيحاول تدمير السفينة؟
Gin!
!غين
Blow Zeff's brains out!
!فجِّر رأس زيف
Do it already!
!أسرِع
B-But the 100 meals he gave us saved our lives!
!لـ-لكنه أنقذ حياتنا بمنحنا مئة وجبة
Gin, you son of a bitch!
!أيها الوغد غين
Hey!
،اسمع
It's not as if I attacked you guys or anything...
...أنا لم أهاجمكم أو ما شابه
I only broke the fin.
.دمّرتُ الزعنفة فحسب
Hey, Cabin Boy! What do you think you're doing?!
ماذا تفعل أيها الفتى العامل؟
Sinking it.
سأغرقها
What?!
ماذا؟
I'm gonna sink this ship.
سأغرق هذه السفينة
– That ain't funny!
!كفاكَ سخافةً
So that's your explanation?!
أهذا تفسيرك؟
Are you crazy?!
أأنت مجنون أيها الوغد؟
If I destroy the ship, there'll be no reason for them to attack.
فكِّر فيها، لن يكون لديهم سبب لمهاجمتكم إن دمرتُ السفينة
What?!
ماذا؟
What do you know?
...ما أدراكَ
The kindness he's shown me...
!عن مدى أهمية الجميل الذي تلقيتُه وعن هذا المطعم؟
You're gonna die for this restaurant?
إذًا فستموت من أجل المطعم؟
Are you stupid?
أأنت أحمق؟
What'd you say?!
ماذا قلت؟
Dying isn't...
...الموت ليس
Dying isn't how you repay kindness!
!الموت ليس أمرًا تردّ به جميلًا
That's not what he saved you for!
!لم يُنقذكَ لهذه الغاية
Being given life and then dying anyway...
...أن تموت بعد إعطائك فرصةً ثانيةً لتعيش
means you're weak!
!يعني ضعفك
Then what else can I do to resolve this?!
أهنالكَ طريقة غيرها لحلّ هذه المسألة إذًا؟
Now, now, you guys...
على رسلكما يا رفيقيَّ
Stop fighting.
كفاكما قتالًا
It's disgraceful for you guys to fight each other now.
مخزيٌ أن تتقاتلا بعد كل ما حدث
Besides, you can't pull any more stunts as long as we have our hostage.
إضافةً لذلك، لا يمكنكما التهور بينما هو رهينتنا
How unfortunate that you're facing the Krieg Pirates.
من سوء حظكم أن خصمكم نحن، قراصنة كريغ
And now my fire pearls will burn you to death!
!فلتموتا حرقًا بنيران لآلئي
Gin!
!غين
Why...
...لماذا
Gin?
يا غين-سان؟
Sorry, Pearl.
أعتذر يا بيرل
Stay down for a bit...
...ابقَ طريحًا قليلًا
Gin!
أستخوننا يا غين؟
I'm sorry, Don Krieg.
أعتذر أيها الدون كريغ
He saved our lives.
فقد أنقذ حياتنا
I don't want him to die like this.
لا أريده أن يموت هكذا
At least...
...على الأقل
At least let me bury him with my own hands.
دعني أدفنه بيدي هاتين
Have you lost your mind,
...أفقدتَ رشدك
Pirate Fleet Commander?
يا قائد أسطول القراصنة؟
So he wasn't just some grunt?
إنه ليس مجرد تابع إذًا؟
He cracked that guy's shield... That's some power...!
!تحطيمه لدرع ذلك المُدرّع لا يعقل، يا لقوته
See? My plan to lure him out worked great!
أرأيت؟ نجح الأمر، إنها خطتي لاستدراجه
Liar!
!كاذب
You really were going to break the ship, weren't you?!
!كانت غايتك تدمير السفينة فعلًا
Sanji!
!سانجي-سان
What?!
نعم؟
I hoped you'd leave here unharmed, but it looks like I won't get my way.
كنتُ أودّك أن تغادر سالمًا لكن يبدو أني لن أحقق مبتغاي
Yeah, so it would seem.
أجل، يبدو كذلك
I'll at least set things right by burying you...
على الأقل يمكنني تصحيح كل شيء
with my own two hands.
بدفنك بيديّ هاتين
Thanks.
شكرًا لك
You piece of shit.
أيها الحثالة
You too, Straw Hat.
أنت أيضًا يا فتى قبعة القش
Well...
...حسنٌ
I won't lose against a wimp like you.
لن أخسر ضد واهنٍ مثلك
You bastard!
!أيها الوغد
What did you just say to our commander?!
ماذا وصفت قائدنا؟
"Piece of shit"?! "Wimp"?! That's some big talk over there!
أيها الضعيف»؟ «واهن»؟ كيف تجرؤان على قول هذا؟»
We're the Krieg Pirates, the strongest crew in the East Blue!
!نحن قراصنة كريغ، الأقوى في الأزرق الشرقي
Isn't that just because you had the most pirates?
أليسَ هذا لكثرة أعدادكم فحسب؟
Oh, boy...
...يا إلهي... أصبتهم في مقتل
So I was right.
كنتُ محقًا إذًا
Son of a bitch!
!أيها الوغد
I'm gonna kill you!
!سأقتلك
Don't mock us!
!كفاكَ سخريةً منّا
Back off!
!تراجعوا
Don Krieg!
!أيها الدون كريغ
But...
...لكن
If you get upset when called weak, it just proves you are weak.
غضبكم بعد وصفكم بالضعفاء يعني صحة الأمر
Only the outcome will determine your strength.
ستحدد النتيجة إن كنتم أقوياء أم ضعفاء
You've got me.
أنا موجود هنا
Don't get so worked up!
!لا تضطربوا كثيرًا
– Y-Yes, sir!
!حـ-حاضر
Gin!
يا غين
Finishing off that cook is your responsibility.
القضاء على ذلك الطباخ مسؤوليتك أنت
I'll take care of that hapless fool over there...
سأتولى أمر ذلك الغبي الساذج
Understood, Don Krieg.
مفهوم أيها الدون كريغ
Hey, brat!
أيها الشقي
I'll make you truly experience the power that conquered the East Blue.
سأُذيقك القوة الحقيقية، التي هيمنت الأزرق الشرقي
I'll teach you just how worthless your so-called devil fruit actually is.
سأعلّمك أن فاكهة الشيطان أو مهما كانت لا فائدة لها
Blah, blah, blah... You talk too much.
...إنك مزعجٌ حقًّا
I'll kick your ass.
سأوسعك ضربًا، الأمر بهذه البساطة
I'm coming over now!
سآتي إليك الآن
Get ready for a thrashing!
!فاستعد للسحق
Impudent brat.
...يا للوقاحة
That chef is cooked.
هذه نهاية ذلك الطباخ
No kidding.
.هذا صحيح
When Gin uses that weapon, it means he's serious.
حملُ غين-سان ذلك السلاح يعني جدّيّته
His nickname is...
...لقبه هو
Hellspawn.
الشيطان
No matter how much his enemy cries or screams,
لا يهم إن صرخ أو بكى عدوه
he mercilessly tortures them to death.
فإنه لَيُعذبه حتى الموت بلا رحمة
He's a demon without a shred of sympathy...
إنه شيطان لا شفقة لديه
I'm sorry, Sanji, but you can't defeat me.
أعتذر يا سانجي-سان، ليس بوسعك هزيمتي
Just keep saying that, small fry.
استمر في هرائك هذا أيها التابع الصغير
Here I come!
ها أنا ذا
You son of a...
...أيها
Sanji!
!سانجي
So long...
...مع السلامة
Now, get lost already!
تقبل الهزيمة فحسب
Yeah! The commander is incredible!
أجل، قائدنا مذهل فعلًا
Crush him, Gin!
اسحقه يا غين-سان
– Sanji!
!سانجي
Die!
!مُت
That cook landed a blow on Gin...
...تمكن ذلك الطباخ من إصابة غين-سان
Is Gin gonna lose, too...?
...لا يعقل أن يُهزم غين-سان أيضًا
You fools...
...حمقى
You've seen what he can do time and again, haven't you?
ما الذي رأيتموه بأم أعينكم حتى الآن؟
Gin is a coolheaded demon that has earned my trust.
غين شيطان هادئ وضعتُ ثقتي به
That's exactly why I appointed him as your commander.
ولهذا عينتُه قائدًا لكم
He'll show his true colors soon.
سيُظهر معدنه الحقيقي قريبًا
How do you think Sanji's holding up?
هل سانجي بخير حقًّا؟
Terribly, of course!
بالطبع لا
With this on top of the shield guy's attacks,
،بسبب هجمات ذلك المدرع
he's got at least five or six broken ribs.
فلا بد أنه يعاني من خمسة أو ستة أضلاع مكسورة
Those skewered dumplings...
...سيخ الدانغو تلك
aren't as good...
...ليست جيدة
as I thought.
...كما توقعتها
Is that the best the commander can do?
أهذا أفضل ما لدى القائد؟
What's he doing at a time like this?
ماذا يفعل في مثل هذا الوقت؟
Alright! He's wide open for an ass-kicking!
حسنٌ، إنه مفتوح للركل الجبّار
Don't strain yourself.
لا تجهد نفسك
You bastard! Do you want to fight me or not?!
أيها الوغد، أتنوي قتالي فعلًا؟
Fight you?
أنوي قتالك؟
I don't see the need.
لا حاجة لهذا
What's needed is a means to kill.
ما أحتاجه هو النية للقتل
That's all.
هذا كل شيء
That's a man's way of showing force, boy.
وهذه هي القوة المُتمتّع بها البشر
Remember it, you damn monkey!
تذكر هذا أيها القرد اللعين
What?!
ماذا؟
Take a monkey lightly, and you'll get scratched!
إن استخففتَ بقرد فسيخدشك
Sanji!
!سانجي
Get him!
!نل منه
Dammit! That shield guy over-tenderized him!
سُحقًا، ليته لم يتلق أضرارًا من ذلك المُدرّع
And he must have taken a dozen hits from those iron balls.
تلقى عشر ضربات على الأقل من تلك الكرات الحديدية حتى الآن
You really do whatever you want...
...تفعل ما يحلو لك
you small fry!
!أيها التابع الصغير
Damn...
...تبًّا
He's really strong...
...إنه قوي فعلًا
Time to end this!
!سأنهي أمرك الآن
Don't struggle anymore.
...لا تكافح أكثر
What was that?! Pity?
أهذه شفقة؟
Don't underestimate me!
!لا تستخف بي
Gin!
!غين-سان
Sanji!
!سانجي
Oh, no! He can't even bear the impact from his own attacks anymore!
لا فائدة، إنه لا يستطيع حتى تحمل صدمات هجماته
That's our Gin!
كما عهدنا من قائدنا غين-سان
You...
...وغد
damn bastard...
...لعين
I can't do it, Don Krieg!
ليس بوسعي فعلها أيها الدون كريغ
Gin...
...غين
I can't...
...ليس بوسعي
kill this man...
...قتله
What'd you say?!
ماذا تقول؟
It was...
...فقد كانت
It... It was...
...كانت
the first time for me...
...أول مرةٍ
I'm so ashamed.
...المعذرة
Sorry...
المعذرة... شكرًا لك... ظننتُني سأموت
I thought I was done for.
...ظننتُ أنّ أمري انتهى
Delicious...
...لذيذ... هذا لذيذ
I've never eaten food so delicious.
هذه أوّل مرّة أتذوّق فيها طعامًا لذيذًا كهذا
It's damn tasty, isn't it?
إنّهُ لذيذٌ جدًا، صحيح؟
Sorry.
...معذرةً
You're gonna get in trouble for giving me a free meal, aren't you?
سيوبخك لأنّك أطعمتني مجانًا، صحيح؟
No proof, no trouble.
لا دليل يدعوه لِيُوبّخني
No one had ever...
...لم يُعاملني أي أحد
treated me so kindly before...
...بذلك اللطف من قبل
So...
...لذلك
I can't kill this man!
ليس بوسعي قتله
Come back any time!
!تعالَ في أيّ وقتٍ
I know...
...أعلم
I don't intend to betray you.
لا أودّ خيانتك
I don't think what we've done up until now is wrong, either...
...لا أعتقد أن ما فعلناه حتى الآن خاطئ أيضًا
I still respect your power and appreciate you as well.
ما زلت أحترم قوتك وأقدرك كثيرًا أيضًا
I was overjoyed when you put your trust in my strength
كنتُ سعيدًا جدًا عندما وضعتَ ثقتك بي وعينتني قائدًا
So I've followed your orders, and that's not going to change...
لهذا امتثلتُ لأوامرك وسأواصل ذلك من الآن فصاعدًا أيضًا
But...
...لكن
He's the only person I can't bring myself to kill!
!لا أستطيع... قتل هذا الرجل تحديدًا
Don Krieg...
...أيها الدون كريغ
If the circumstances allow it...
...إن سمحت، أيُمكن
I'd like for us to spare this ship... this restaurant.
أيُمكن ترك هذه السفينة والمطعم وشأنهما
You son of a bitch!
!أيها الوغد
As if defying my orders wasn't enough, now you're lecturing me?!
!لم تكن معارضة أوامري كافيةً فأراكَ تُسمعني محاضرة أيضًا
What's gotten into you?!
!يا مجنون
How disappointing...
...هذا مخيب للآمال
There's nothing I detest more than sympathy and morality.
فأنا أمقتُ الأخلاق والتعاطف
Haven't I always said that?
ألم أقل هذا دومًا؟
Clear the way, men.
ابتعدوا يا رجال
Don! That's...
...أيها الدون، هذا
O-Oh no! MH5!
!إ-إم إتش 5
That's the most deadly nerve gas!
!إنه أشدّ سلاح غاز سام
What?!
ماذا؟
Nerve gas?!
!غاز سام؟
Put your masks on!
!الأقنعة
Hurry up!
!بسرعة
We'll die too!
!سنُقتل أيضًا
To use a weapon like that...
...استعماله له لا يعقل
That's despicable, you bastard!
!هذه حقارة أيها الوغد
Do you know what'll happen if you use that?!
أتدري ما سيحدث عند استعماله؟
Stop whining, you idiots.
كفاكم نواحًا أيها الأغبياء، فهذا لا يهم
This is a battle!
هذه معركة
Winning is the only objective.
الفوز هو الغاية السامية
Foul play? Fighting dirty?
أعمال شائنة؟ قذرة؟
There's no such thing!
ما العيب في ذلك؟
Might makes right.
الصواب مع القوة
The ends will always justify the means!
النتيجة هي كل شيء مهما كانت الوسيلة
So what if I'm using nerve gas?
سواء أكان غازًا سامًا أو غيره، لا يهم إلا الفوز
That's power.
هذه هي القوة
What a rotten bastard...!
...يا لفظاعة ذلك الوغد
Throw that gas mask away!
!ارمِ قناع الغاز
You're no longer one of us.
فما عدتَ واحدًا منا
Die!
!مُت
I won't let you shoot that nerve gas!
!لن أسمح لك بإطلاق ذلك الغاز السام
Stop scuttling about, anchor boy!
!كفاك ركضًا أيها الفتى المرساة
D-Dammit!
!سُـ-سُحقًا
Gin!
!غين
You don't have to listen to what that wimp says!
!لستَ مضطرًا للاستماع لكلام ذلك الضعيف
I'm kicking his ass here and now!
!سأوسعه ضربًا الآن
Don't mock Don Krieg!
!لا تستخف بالدون كريغ
He is unmatched.
إنه الرجل الأقوى
You can't defeat him.
لا يمكنك هزيمته
Come to your senses, you idiot!
عد إلى رشدك يا أهبل
That man is trying to kill you!
يحاول ذلك الرجل قتلك
I deserve it...
...أستحق ذلك
since I couldn't fulfill my duty,
،بما أنني لم أحقق هدفي
having shamelessly lost to emotion...
...واستمعتُ لعواطفي
This is...
!هذا... هذا عقاب أستحقه بالكامل
Gin!
!غين
Why... Why?
لماذا... لماذا؟
So you show your pride at the end...
أظهرتَ فخرك في النهاية
But it's too late.
لكن الأوان فات
Die together with that cook!
مُت مع ذلك الطباخ
Nerve gas...
قنبلة الغاز السام المميتة
M...
...إم
H...
...إتش
5!
!5
Here it comes!
!إنها قادمة
Dive into the sea!
!غوصوا في البحر
Chef Zeff! Get inside!
!لندخل المطعم أيها المالك
I'm borrowing these.
سأستعيرهما
Sanji! Gin!
سانجي، غين
Use these!
!استعملاهما
Cabin Boy!
!أيها العامل
Now for mine!
!والآن دوري
Wh-What?!
!ماذا؟ غاص جميعهم في البحر
What do I do?! What do I do?!
ماذا أفعل؟ ماذا أفعل؟ ماذا أفعل؟
This...
هذه هي القوة
I... I'm saved...
...نـ-نجوت
Good thing I found that mask when I did...
جيدٌ أنني وجدتُ قناعًا في آخر لحظة
Wh-What a crazy bastard...
...يـ-يا له من وغد لا يعقل
I can't believe he used nerve gas in battle...
لا أصدق أنه استعمل غازًا سامًا في معركة
H-He's a devil...
إنه شيطان
Yeah, no human being would do something like that!
نعم، ما كان أي بشري ليُقدم على أمرٍ كهذا
Are Sanji and the cabin boy okay?
هل سانجي وذلك العامل بخير؟
Not sure...
...لا أدري
Look! The poison mist is clearing up!
!انظر، سحابة السم تتلاشى
Gin!
!غين
Let go...
...اترك
Let go of the mask!
!اترك القناع
Gin!
!غين
Where's your mask?!
أين قناعك؟
Did you...
قناعك... هل أعطيتني إياه؟
Gin!
!غين
What an idiot.
يا لحماقتك
That pain is the result of feeling indebted over getting a bite to eat.
أنت تتألم الآن لأنك تشعر أنك تدين له لأنه أطعمك فحسب
Well, I guess idiots don't learn until they die, huh?
حسنٌ، أعتقد أن الحمقى لا يتعلمون حتى يموتون
Don...
أ-أيها الدون كريغ
Gin...
...غين
Gin, it seems...
...غين... يبدو
It seems like you picked the wrong man to follow...
يبدو أنك اخترت الرجل الخطأ لتمنحه ولاءك
You're actually sympathizing with that scum?
هل تتعاطفان فعلًا مع ذلك الحثالة الغبي؟
Scum?!
حثالة؟
That's right.
صحيح
An idiot who loses sight of our goal and can't follow my orders
أحمق تخلى عن أهدافنا ولا يمتثل لأوامري
is worthless to me.
صار بلا فائدة عندي
There's no guarantee he won't betray me again.
لا يوجد ما يضمن أنه لن يخونني ثانيةً
It's love that drives me to put him down now. Don't you see?
خلّصته من بؤسه بدافع الحب
I... I never imagined the don would actually kill the commander...
مـ-ما حسبتُ أن الدون قد يقتل القائد فعلًا
Th-That can't be true...
!لـ-لا يُعقل... ذلك مستحيل
Gin is his right-hand man!
!غين-سان هو ذراعه اليمنى
That's right.
صحيح
No one has been more faithful to the don than Gin!
لا يوجد من هو أكثر ولاءً للدون من غين-سان
Even back then...
...وحتى في ذلك الوقت
When Fullbody and the Marines came after us as we escaped the Grand Line...
وعندما طاردتنا سفينة فولوبودي من البحرية حينها
Yeah...
...نعم
He acted as a decoy all by himself, pretending to be the don...
لعب دور الطعم وحده وتظاهر أنه الدون حينها
He always risked his life fighting for Don Krieg...
...طالما خاطر بحياته مقاتلًا من أجل الدون كريغ
I never imagined the don would try to kill him...
ما حسبتُ أن يقتله فعلًا
How evil...
...فظيع
Patty! We have an antidote, don't we?!
باتي، لدينا ترياق، صحيح؟
Antidote? Well, we have medicine for food poisoning.
نعم لدينا، لكنه يصلح للتسمم الغذائي
It doesn't matter! Just bring it here!
!لا يهم الآن، أحضره إلى هنا
Idiot!
!أحمق
If you wanna save him, put the mask on him right away!
ضع القناع عليه فورًا إن أردتَ إنقاذه
It should have some sort of detoxifying effect!
يجدر أن يكون فيه تأثير مزيل للسموم
Let's get him to the second floor and have him just breathe.
أحضره إلى الطابق الثاني ودعه يتنفس جيّدًا
If there's a chance to save him, that's the only way!
إن كانت هنالك فرصة لإنقاذه، فهذه الطريقة الوحيدة
Hurry up, Patty and Carne!
!بسرعة يا باتي وكارني
Alright already!
!فهمتُ فلا تصرخ
Me too?!
لمَ أنا أيضًا؟
It's no use.
لا فائدة
He'll live for another hour at most.
حتى إن بقي حيًا فسيدوم ذلك لساعة على الأكثر
Don't you dare die, Gin.
إيَّاكَ الموت يا غين
Don't let someone like him kill you!
!لا تدع رجلًا مثله يقتلك
Cling to life! Got that?!
تمسك بالحياة، مفهوم؟
I'll kick his ass for you!
!سأوسعه ضربًا من أجلك
D-Don't...
لـ-لا تفعل
You can't...
فأنت لا تستطيع
defeat him...!
هزيمته
Cool down!
اهدأ
Attacking head-on would be playing right into his hands. You'll die!
!إن مهاجمته مباشرةً بمثابة رمي نفسك بين قبضتيه، ستموت
I won't die.
لن أموت
Shoot me all you want!
هيا تقدم وأطلق بقدر ما تشاء
Hey!
!مهلًا
Such a fool...
...يا لحماقته
The easiest enemy to kill is one who's in a frenzy.
إن الأعداء فاقدي الرشد أسهل الأعداء قتلًا
The sea is your hell, anchor boy. You're heading toward...
...البحر جحيمك أيها الفتى المرساة، إنك تتجه نحو
Here comes...
...ها هو ذا
Bombs!
!قنابل
...your graveyard!
!قبرك
My graveyard?!
قبري؟
Oh, no! Get out of there, Cabin Boy!
!كلا، ابتعد أيها العامل
He got hit!
!أصابه
He's dead.
...مات
Cabin Boy...
...أيها العامل
You little...
...هذا الوغد
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Hit me...
...اضربني
Here it comes!
!ها هو
...if you dare!
!إن استطعت...
That's dirty!
...يا للقذارة! إنه
Pistol!
بيستول
What?!
ماذا؟
Don Krieg is down!
!هُزم الدون كريغ
What the hell is this guy?!
ما ماهية هذا الفتى؟
He punched the don through his spiked cape!
!ضربه وهو يرتدي عباءة الأشواك
Ouch...
...ذلك مؤلم
This is unreal...
هذا غير عادي
We've never seen the don brought to his knees...
لم نرَ الدون كريغ جاثيًا على ركبتيه قبلًا
He hit the don in his face!
ضرب الدون على وجهه
Right through his Kenzanspike Mantle, too!
هذا رغم إنه يرتدي عباءة الأشواك
C-Can you believe that?!
هـ-هـ-هل تصدقون هذا؟
Is this...
...أهذا
my graveyard?
قبري؟
Or is it...
...أم
yours?
قبرك؟
My...
...قبري
graveyard?!
!أنا؟
Don't think...
...لا تفكر حتى
you can send me to my grave with this.
أن بوسعك إرسالي لقبري بأشياءٍ كهذا
I'm not gonna die here.
لن أموت هنا
He's unhinged...
...إنه مجنون
You see idiots like that every once in a while...
...نرى أغبياء مثله من حين لآخر
ones who will fight to the death once they've set their eyes on a target.
أغبياء يقاتلون حتى الموت لمجرّد هدف نصب أعينهم
Fight...
يقاتلون حتى الموت؟
You're in trouble if someone like that becomes your enemy.
ستكون في مصيبة إن كان رجلٌ كهذا عدوك
But you know,
،ولكن اعلم هذا
win or lose,
،سواء خسروا أو فازوا
I like guys like him!
!فإن أمثاله يروقون لي